Hello everyone! I'm Anna Yamamoto from Equal Love
Kisaya Tanida of Not equal me
I am Ayumi Ozawa of Yerry Equal Jai!
We are very happy to announce that we have started a collaboration campaign with
POBO, a service provided by KDDI Corporation, has started a collaboration campaign.
I'm very happy to be able to visit your office this time.
Thank you very much.
It's very rare to see two people together.
The combination of the two of us.
First time. I'm so excited.
Look how cute they are.
They're so cute.
They have dolls, too.
We've never collaborated with a company before.
I'm very happy.
Thank you very much.
In this campaign, we were able to shoot a collaboration video in this way.
I was able to shoot a video of the collaboration
We also made a topping for the Iconojoy Channel collaboration
We made toppings for the Iconojoy Channel collaboration, and
Original photo and autographed goods for those who purchase the toppings.
Original photos and autographed goods
and tickets to watch the limited video streaming.
We hope you enjoy it!
The details will be explained in the latter half of this video.
I will explain it all in detail later in this video.
Thank you very much!
This is the first video of the collaboration campaign
This is the first video of the collaboration campaign.
POBO's management staff will explain
about this campaign.
But first
Before that
We've got three groups here.
Since we're recording with all the members together
I'd like to make a project.
Yay!
In addition to the three of us.
Julie will be joining us.
I'd like to surprise her.
Wow!
Surprise!
I'm so happy.
I wanted to set you up.
I wish I could have done it.
I don't know... if it's a surprise in reverse or something...
It's scary, isn't it?
Scary.
It makes you distrustful of people.
I know.
The three of us will work together.
I'd like to surprise you.
Under the title
Without Julie noticing.
"Sneaking into a fake recording without Julie noticing.
Yay!
So, Julie...
Aimi and...
Yes!
About the campaign
I'm going to film the POBO staff
about the campaign.
Right?
That's how we call them.
And Sayaka and I
We each disguised ourselves as a staff member.
Yes, sir.
So that Julie won't notice us.
We're going to try three missions without Julie noticing.
Yes, sir.
Aimi, as a trickster.
You'll have to guide Julie a little better.
And support us.
Yes, please.
I'll be the POBO staff, by the way.
And Sayayan...
I'll disguise myself as a YouTube staff member.
I'll disguise myself.
I'd like to announce the mission that I'm going to challenge on the way.
I'd like to announce some of the challenges we'll face along the way.
I'll start with me.
First one.
As a POBO staff member
I will exchange business cards with the agency staff.
Oh!
What's your name or something like that?
Anna Yamamoto, as you'd expect.
Yes, that's right.
I think I'll change my name and do it.
Please look forward to it.
And secondly, I'd like to give you some tea.
Maybe water.
I'm going to serve tea or something to drink.
And the third one is...
I'm going to go and give an earful to the employee sitting in front of Julie.
I'm going to go give an earful.I'm going to go give you an earful.
Heh.
I'm running an errand.
Yeah.
I'd like to make an appearance before
Oh!
Let's go ahead and announce your mission.
Yes, my mission number one.
I'd like to give the script to Jerry.
I think it's pretty close, so I'm going to be really close.
I'll be very careful with my movements.
Second, I'm going to take a picture for social networking.
I'll be right in front of her.
There will be a lot of eye contact, so I'll be using my phone to make sure of my face.
I'll use my phone to make sure of my face.
Yes, my face is so small that I can hide it.
Lastly, I'd like to fix the gold microphone.
This is the gold microphone.
That's right.
I want to surprise you.
Okay, let's go for it.
I'll do my best.
Me and Anna, we'll be in disguise!
I'm off!
Well, it looks like you two are done with your listening session, so I'd like to call you up.
Anna-san, Saya-san.
Ha-ha-ha!
Cute!
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, Saya.
So cute!
It's overflowing with cute.
And a mask.
I'll wear a mask, so you can trust me.
Julie, you know, you've got good instincts.
She's the most perceptive one here at Joy.
Oh, my God, what am I going to do?
The last time we did a surprise on the Joy Channel with just NyaJoy...
I was already suspicious the day before.
Oh, my God!
It was hard work.
That's why it's Julie today.
With the number of staff members here, they're going to find out.
Oh, my God.
About three times as many.
We'll work together.
We'll do our best.
Good morning. Best regards.
Good morning. This is New Leake Original. Pleased to meet you.
Excuse me. Thank you very much for your cooperation.
Pleased to meet you.
I'm nervous.
There's a camera leg here.
I hope it's all right.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you.
Please talk to our online staff.
Thank you for waiting. Mr. Big Sizer, you are in.
Yes, I am. Pleased to meet you.
Good to start. Please.
Lamps.
I have lamps.
Nice to meet you. My name is Moyat. Footage.
I'll do it.
Thank you for waiting.
Ichida-san, please pick up the phone.
My name is Tomoyasu. Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you
Sorry, I changed it.
It's Mr. Econoid's specs.
That's great!
That's great.
And thank you very much for covering the piano of Near Joy.
Please do.
I hope I use them all.
Yes, I'm glad.
I look forward to working with you.
Actually, but my ex is also a huge fan.
That's right.
I'm sorry I just took your picture first.
Yes, I'm sorry, please.
Just make sure it's in the right shape.
In the middle.
Is that okay?
Yes, please.
Okay, I'll give you three. Three, two, yes.
Okay, here we go. Three, two, yes.
Thank you very much.
This character is cute, isn't he?
Yes, he is.
Were you in the same space?
Yes, he was there the whole time.Yes, I was at the venue the whole time.
It's been a while, everyone.
It's been a long time.
It's nice to see you again,
I was looking forward to it,
I was looking forward to seeing you again.
I was leaning in.
I'm sorry. We're running out of time,
Please come in a little earlier.
Excuse me. Just a minute.
Okay, first of all,
Wow. Pop-pop.
Yes.
I'll let you get to know.
This time, I'm going to ask you to join us,
to some sort of online service.
I am interviewing for an online service,
Yes.
Face users
Ah...
What?
Noise?
Can I have a word with you?
Saya?
No!
Hello!
Ha-ha-ha!
Did I ask too much?
Did I just get away with it?
So, Julie.
Julie?
Yes, Julie?
Surprise!
Yes!
Yeah!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Oh, my God, Julie, it's so hard.
From the way I feel.
It's a realization I'm not sure I'll be saying much about anytime soon.
Ha-ha-ha!
Maybe I should just yell a little.
Don't be real reflective.
Well, when did you notice?
I don't know. It was kind of in the back.
That was something like...
What? Back view?
That's why your face was so small.
What?
Did I give you away?
Oh, that's old.
I thought we had enough time.
And the rest of the staff...
We thought we could do it.
We were so confident that we could do it.
Well, come to the front.
There?
What?
So, Julie, how did you feel about the surprise?
I didn't expect it, but this collaboration with Mr. Pomo was not a surprise.
Yes, it was. I'm glad. Now, let's talk about the details of this campaign with the Pomo staff.
We will also talk about the gift, so please watch until the end. Please watch the video until the end.
I will talk about the details of the campaign.
Our very own Aimi made the flip card for this campaign.
I wrote it.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Aimi-chan made it for us, and we will do it while looking at this.
First of all, here it is.
What is Bobo?
It's cute.
Amazing. You made it very well. Easy to see.
I know there are some viewers who don't know about Bobo, so I think it would be better to ask the staff about it, right?
Yes, please. Please do.
Thank you very much.
Bobo is now offering a service under the name Bobo 2.0,
KDDI Corporation offers a smartphone plan exclusively for online use.
In the past, cell phone contracts were done in stores,
Bobo is an online-only service, so you can register only through the application.
We offer a zero-cost basic plan,
We had a basic fee of zero yen, so people could buy the data they wanted and use it only when they wanted to use it,
This is what we call "topping up" in Bobo.
I think you already have a contract for the smartphone you own,
Bobo is the second round of the contract, and the basic fee is 0 yen,
If you have a second round of Bobo, the basic fee is 0 yen, so you can use Bobo to buy more gigs when you run out of gigs,
This is one of the major features of this service.
That's great!
Just because I like it.
I love it. We also spend a lot of money on Giga.
We spend a lot of money.I see a lot of money.
It's good because I can do it plus the amount of money I want to buy.
This time, it's a limited offer until June 19,
I will be releasing a collaboration topping with the iconoi Actress Channel,
We will be releasing the toppings in 2.0,
Thank you very much!
We hope everyone will be able to purchase it.
When will it be available?
It should be out by the time this video is released,
Please check it out.
I think there is a link in the summary section, so please check it out.
Now let's turn the page.
Here is the next one!
There is a special offer!
Oh!
I'm curious.
As the staff mentioned earlier,
I've heard that it comes with a lot of perks,
Sayayan, may I be introduced to you?
Yes! I will introduce them to you.
I would like to turn to the first one.
Iconojoy Channel Collaboration Photo & 500MB of data that can be used for 3 days!
So, use the Iconojoy campaign code that is out now,
For new subscribers to Almost 2.0,
We are giving away 500MB of data that can be used for 3 days and a photo from the Iconojoy Channel collaboration.
Glad to hear it. Thank you very much.
So, you can download the app from the link in the overview section,
Please check it out.
Thank you very much.
It's a lot of fun, and I'm really interested in the collaboration photo.
Amazing. I wonder what it looks like.
I am sure it will be posted somewhere here, somewhere in the video, by now.
The characters are on it together,
You are all so cute, so please get it.
Please do.
Then I would like to go to the next page.
Please get it.
Invitation to the Pobo Collaboration YouTube streaming after talk.
Anyone who actually purchased the collaboration toppings,
You can watch the after talk of the Pobo Collaboration distribution that will be aired on July 7.
Sounds good. Rare, isn't it?
Rare.
Even on Tanabata.
Tanabata.
It's not often that the members of Ikonoijoy get together,
It's not often that the members of Icono Joy get together for a limited broadcast,
I hope you are looking forward to it.
Please look forward to it.
We will be taking your questions and requests, and we will also be sending out wide checks signed by all of the members,
We will also have wide checks signed by all the members,
There will also be a raffle to win a stuffed animal that will be introduced during the live broadcast.
It's gorgeous.
It's a big, big luxury,
Please check out the July 7 broadcast.
Please do.
And now, I'd like to hand over to Juri.
Please let me turn it over to Juri.
Let me turn it over.
Ta-da! I heard that there are also special offers to choose from,
That's right. In addition to the ticket to watch the live concert and the lottery ticket for the goods, there is one more benefit that you can choose,
Here it is.
The first 1,000 people to arrive will receive a Popo Collaboration design drink burda,
or a signed Popo plush toy for the first 30 winners of the drawing.
I want it.
So, first of all, the plushie is this girl.
Cute.
Big.
It's big, and we only have one of each,
Each group will receive a stuffed animal signed by all the members of the group.
Amazing.
It's big and comfortable to touch.
It's kind of comforting, isn't it? I was greeted by her when I went backstage earlier,
It heals me.
It heals me. It's sticky.
And the drink holder, which is a first-come, first-served present,
The design of the drink holder has not been decided yet,
So I'm allowed to decide now,
We will choose one.
We?
Oh, no.
I say we can decide.
Cute.
Everyone is cute.
Three colors are cute.
Because what are we going to do?
We decide.
How do we decide?
Rock, paper, scissors.
Rock, paper, scissors?
You're gonna leave it to a sentence like that?
You want to try it once?
Can I say "once"?
Ready?
First, goo, then rock, paper, scissors.First, goo, then rock-paper-scissors hoi.
It's Aiko, right?
First goo, then rock, paper, scissors.
No.
Even though she always loses.
But I don't want her to have a hard time,
Let's all decide together.
Thank you.
Okay.
Wouldn't it be great if we had this?
They'd be great.
None of them.
But I've decided.
You're early.
First-come-first-served.
He's cute.
The one that caught my attention.
Me too, though.
I've decided too.
Shall we go then?
Yes.
Ready.
Here.
This is amazing.
Oh, man.
Isn't it amazing?
It's so cute.
We decided at once, didn't we?
I knew it!
It's wonderful.
Everything is so cute.
I'm so happy.
It's unanimous.
Then please use this cute design.
Please do.
I said one of them was a little different.
Wow.
My hands are shaking.
Then, please make Ai-chan the last one with the pendulum.
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
Gorgeous shape.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
Now, here is the last one.
The present program in the After Talk.
Sayan-san introduced this one earlier,
This is a campaign for a gift in the limited after-talk program that can be viewed by those who purchased the collaboration toppings,
This is a campaign for winning a check signed by all the members and a small stuffed animal.
We hope you will watch the program.
Thank you very much for your cooperation.
So, there will be a lot of special offers.
And we are getting closer to 2023 than ever before.
I hope we can all get excited about it.
Please check out the special page in the overview section.
I look forward to working with you.
That's all for today's video.
See you all again.
Bye bye.
Yes, well, karekuma.
Chie, lie.
That's a lie. What time did Aimin come in?
Ten o'clock.
What?
He came in at 10:00.
Sorry. What's wrong?
What? Why?
I was eating.
What? It's totally fine.
Please eat at all. It's important to eat.